[Music]
[音乐]
hi everyone my name is Mathura Vevey and
大家好，我叫Mathura Vevey，
I'm a developer on the spring bootie mat
我是Spring Bootie Mat的开发人员
favela
贫民窟
I hope you're having a good conference
我希望你会谈愉快
so far and in today's talk we're going
到目前为止，在今天的演讲中，我们要
to be taking a closer look at what
仔细看看
really happens when a spring boot
spring boot 真的发生了
application runs what goes on behind the
应用程序将运行
scenes a lot of times we hear things
很多次我们听到的场景
like spring boot has too much magic we
就像 spring boot 有太多的魔力，我们
know it does a lot out of the box but we
知道开箱即用，但是我们
don't really know what's going on we see
真的不知道发生了什么
developers just if things don't work
开发人员，即使事情不起作用
they stick on some annotations and leave
他们贴上一些注释并离开
them there if things work and then new
他们在那里，如果一切正常，然后新的
developers come onto the team they don't
开发人员加入他们没有的团队
dare to touch the annotations because
敢于触摸注释，因为
they're too scared to break things so I
他们太害怕打破东西，所以我
just want to show you that there is no
只想告诉你没有
such thing as magic
诸如魔术之类的东西
it's all code and you can all look at it
都是代码，大家都可以看一下
debug it and make sense out of it so
调试它并使其有意义
before we get started with the demo I
在开始演示之前，我
want to show you what this getting
想告诉你这有什么
started experiences that I'm talking
开始谈论我的经历
about most of you are actually familiar
你们大多数人实际上都很熟悉
with starter spring or iOS so I'm just
与 Spring 初学者或iOS，所以我只是
going to use that to create a new
将使用它来创建一个新的
application I'm using IntelliJ but you
我正在使用IntelliJ的应用程序，但是你
can use any other IDE or even go to
可以使用任何其他IDE，甚至可以转到
startup spring got IO to generate on
启动Spring获得了IO
your project and I'm gonna call it
您的项目，我将其命名为
they're more 21 because I have 20 other
他们多21岁，因为我还有20岁
demos I'm just gonna select the web
演示，我要选择网络
starter for this simple demo and finish
这个简单的演示的入门和完成
so as a lot of you are familiar with
所以你们很多人都熟悉
this structure of a spring good
这种Spring 的结构很好
application we have the spring wood
应用我们有Spring 木
starter web and there's a demo
入门网站，并有一个演示
application class that gets created for
为之创建的应用程序类
you when you generate your project from
您从中生成项目时
start of spring or IO so the spring good
Spring 或IO的开始，所以 Spring 好
application annotation is basically what
应用程序注释基本上是什么
gives you a lot of the goodness that you
给你很多的好处
get out of the box with when you run the
当您运行
spring boot application and I'm just
spring boot 应用程序，我只是
gonna run this
要运行这个
so as expected it starts up on Tomcat by
如预期的那样，它在Tomcat上通过
default on port 8080 which means that
默认在端口8080上，这意味着
your application is up and running and
您的应用程序已启动并正在运行，
ready to serve web requests it's kind of
准备服务于网络请求
interesting because we literally didn't
有趣，因为我们实际上并没有
have to do much and we have a running
必须做很多事情，我们正在跑步
application on Tomcat obviously it's not
Tomcat上的应用程序显然不是
going to release of anything useful at
将发布任何有用的东西
the moment because we don't have any
那一刻因为我们没有任何东西
controllers or anything but it is a
控制器或其他任何东西，但这是一个
running application without having to do
无需运行应用程序
too much this can seem a bit magical I
我觉得这太神奇了
suppose if you don't really understand
假设你不是很了解
what's going on behind the scenes so the
幕后发生了什么，所以
idea is to rebuild this application that
想法是重建这个应用程序
we just saw running and we have all the
我们刚刚看到跑步，我们拥有了所有
technology we're going to start building
我们将要开始构建的技术
the application from scratch and as we
从头开始的应用程序
rebuild it you'll sort of see what
重建它，你会看到什么
spring what spring boot was actually
Spring 实际上是 spring boot
doing for you behind the scenes and what
在幕后为您做些什么
you don't need to do when you use spring
使用Spring 时不需要做
boot to get the application running so
启动以使应用程序运行，以便
let's start from scratch when I say
我说从头开始
scratch I'm still gonna use some
从头开始，我还是会用一些
components of spring boot because I only
spring boot 的组件，因为我只
have 50 minutes so I'm still going to
有50分钟，所以我仍然要
use the spring application run method
使用spring应用程序运行方法
but I'm not going to use any of the
但我不会使用任何
spring boot application annotation or
Spring Boot应用程序注释或
any of the auto configuration stuff that
任何自动配置的东西
you get with spring boot to begin with
你从 spring boot 开始
and then we'll start building the app
然后我们将开始构建应用
and as we start building the application
当我们开始构建应用程序时
you see what needs to be added and you
您会看到需要添加的内容，然后
sort of see what the thought process was
有点看思维过程是什么
behind some of the spring boot
在一些 spring boot 后面
annotations and features is the font
注释和功能是字体
okay I guess I can't really see you so
好吧，我想我真的看不到你
I'll assume it's okay so it's not really
我认为这还可以，所以不是真的
live coding I have a bunch of commits
实时编码，我有很多提交
lined up so we'll go checking out each
排队，所以我们将检查每个
commit and adding things as we need to
提交并添加所需的东西
add them so just a quick look at the
添加它们，以便快速浏览一下
Palm D'Or XML
Palm D'Or XML
it's similar to the application that was
它类似于以前的应用程序
generated from star s finger I oh it has
从星星的手指产生的
the spring would start of web and the
Spring 将开始网络和
application class is a bit different it
应用程序类有点不同
still uses spring application and the
仍然使用spring应用程序，并且
main method but it's not using at spring
主要方法，但 Spring 不使用
boot application so now if we run this
启动应用程序，所以现在如果我们运行此程序
application it fails and the failure is
应用程序失败，失败是
that it's unable to start a servlet web
无法启动servlet网站
server application contacts due to
服务器应用程序联系人由于
missing servlet web server factory being
缺少Servlet Web服务器工厂
so before we actually go ahead and fix
所以在我们实际进行修复之前
this failure I wanted to give you a
这个失败我想给你
little bit of perspective about what
关于什么的一点看法
this means and for that let's take a
这意味着，为此，让我们采取
quick look at how things were before
快速查看之前的情况
there was an embedded servlet container
有一个嵌入式的servlet容器
that you typically get with a spring
通常是 Spring
good application and what it means to
良好的应用程序及其含义
now have an embedded servlet container
现在有一个嵌入式servlet容器
so previously you used to have this web
所以以前你曾经拥有这个网站
container or such as Tomcat to which you
容器或诸如Tomcat之类的
would deploy a war file and the servlet
将部署war文件和servlet
container would then look for a servlet
然后容器将寻找一个servlet
container initializer within that war
那场战争中的容器初始化器
and spring has its own server container
Spring有自己的服务器容器
initializer implementation which then
初始化器实现
looks for a web application initializer
寻找一个Web应用程序初始化程序
and one of the web application
和其中一个Web应用程序
initializers is one that registers a
初始值设定项是注册一个
dispatcher servlet with the servlet
带有servlet的调度程序servlet
container so that thing this used to
容器，所以这东西过去
register the dispatcher servlet which
注册调度程序servlet
then has access to the web application
然后可以访问Web应用程序
context and all the beans so this used
上下文和所有bean，所以这用了
to be the case when or still is the case
当还是仍然如此时
if you deploy a war file to run on
如果您部署战争文件以在
embedded servlet container now in
嵌入式servlet容器现在在
today's world with spring boot
spring boot 的当今世界
applications you have the embedded
您拥有嵌入式应用程序
server container I think in up until
我一直认为服务器容器
Springwood 1.5 this used to actually be
Springwood 1.5这实际上曾经是
called the embedded web application
称为嵌入式Web应用程序
context but we changed it with spring
上下文，但是我们在 Spring 改变了它
route 2 to be servlet web server
路由2成为servlet Web服务器
application context because there was a
应用程序上下文，因为有一个
reactor
反应堆
counterpart that was added in spring
Spring 添加的对应物
Muthu so this servlet web server
Muthu所以这个Servlet Web服务器
application context is actually an
应用程序上下文实际上是
application context that knows how to
知道如何
bootstrap itself by looking for a server
通过寻找服务器来引导自己
servlet web server factory bean within
servlet Web服务器工厂bean
the application context itself and the
应用程序上下文本身和
servlet web server factory bean will
servlet Web服务器工厂bean将
then give you a web server using some of
然后使用一些
the servlet context initializers that
servlet上下文初始化程序
are available within the application
在应用程序中可用
context itself so the web server is
上下文本身，因此Web服务器是
something such a strong cat undertow
像猫一样强壮的东西
jetty which can be started and stopped
可以启动和停止的码头
and like I mentioned before the web
就像我在网络上提到的
server when it is created it gets a plug
创建服务器时，它将获得一个插件
the servlet context initializers that
servlet上下文初始化程序
are present in the application context
存在于应用程序上下文中
then get applied to the web server as it
然后按原样应用到Web服务器
starts up so again there those are
启动，所以又有那些
registered as beans ok so now that we
注册为 bean 好，所以现在我们
have some perspective about the fact
对事实有一些看法
that because this is a web application
因为这是一个Web应用程序
this servlet web server application
此Servlet Web服务器应用程序
context is looking for this servlet web
上下文正在寻找这个servlet网站
server factory bean to bootstrap itself
服务器工厂Bean自行引导
and start up the embedded servlet
并启动嵌入式servlet
container so let's go ahead and add that
容器，所以我们继续添加
bean
bean 角，扁 bean
so I'm just adding a beam for the
所以我只是为
Tomcats of it web server factory so that
Web服务器工厂的Tomcat，以便
it matches the default of what we got
它匹配我们得到的默认值
with the application that we saw from
与我们从中看到的应用程序
started spring at i/o and re running the
从I / O开始 Spring ，然后重新运行
application so it did start up on Tomcat
应用程序，因此它确实在Tomcat上启动
port 8080 now which is what we would
端口8080现在是我们要的
expect because the applications our
期望，因为我们的应用程序
application context was able to find
应用程序上下文能够找到
this being create the web server and
这是创建Web服务器，
start it up so even though we have and
启动它，即使我们有
have a running server just like I
像我一样有一个正在运行的服务器
mentioned before it's not gonna do
之前提到它不会做
anything really useful it's just gonna
任何真正有用的东西都会
give us a 404 because we don't have any
给我们一个404，因为我们没有
controller mappings to handle these
控制器映射来处理这些
requests so we'll start building this
请求，所以我们将开始构建它
one by one I'm just gonna check out the
我要一一检查
commit which adds a rec rest controller
提交，添加一个rec rest控制器
and it's a very simple restaurant roller
这是一个非常简单的餐厅滚筒
which probably most of you are familiar
你们大多数人可能都很熟悉
with it has just one request mapping to
它只有一个请求映射到
slash and it returns HelloWorld
斜线并返回HelloWorld
so if I run this how many of you think
所以如果我运行这个，你们中有多少人认为
this will actually work and serve
这实际上会工作并服务
HelloWorld one person things River okay
HelloWorld一个人的东西河还好
so it didn't work sorry and it didn't
所以对不起，它也没有
work because we still don't have a lot
工作，因为我们仍然没有很多
of the plumbing that you need to get the
您需要获得的管道
MVC the spring MVC stuff working just
MVC Spring MVC的东西只是工作
adding a rest controller it works in a
添加一个 rest controller ，它在一个
spring good application because spring
Spring 很好的应用，因为 Spring
boot is actually doing a lot of the
引导实际上在做很多
plumbing for you but now because we're
为您服务，但现在因为我们
building from scratch we have to do it
从头开始构建，我们必须这样做
ourselves so the first thing that I'm
自己，所以我的第一件事
going to do is add this at enable web
要做的就是在启用网站上添加
MVC up at the annotation and that will
MVC在注释上，这将
basically import all the web MVC
基本上导入所有Web MVC
configuration that you need for handling
您需要处理的配置
this request so
这个要求
let's run it again so it still doesn't
让我们再次运行它，以便它仍然不会
work and the last thing actually that
工作和最后一件事
you need to do is add a dispatcher
您需要做的是添加一个调度程序
servlet so the dispatcher servlet we
servlet，所以调度程序servlet我们
look into a look into it a little bit
稍微看一下
later in the slides is the central
在幻灯片的后面是中心
dispatcher for for HTTP request which
HTTP请求的调度程序
knows how to handle your request and
知道如何处理您的请求，并且
then route them to the right controller
然后将它们路由到正确的控制器
so once we add the dispatcher solid beam
所以一旦我们添加了调度员实心光束
it does work and it gives you hello
它确实起作用，并且给您打招呼
world so that was actually quite a bit
世界，所以实际上
of groundwork that we had to do to get
我们要做的基础工作
just a simple rest controller working
只是一个简单的 rest controller 工作
but you don't really have to think about
但你真的不必考虑
if you were using the add spring boot
如果您正在使用添加 spring boot
application annotation this would have
应用程序注释
automatically been done for you but this
自动为您完成，但这
is actually some of what is going on
实际上是正在发生的事情
behind the scenes when the application
当幕后应用
starts up as a web app so we looked a
作为一个网络应用程序启动，所以我们看起来
little bit at how when the servlet web
一点点介绍如何在servlet Web上运行
server application context starts up it
服务器应用程序上下文启动它
applies the servlet context initializer
应用Servlet上下文初始化器
beans to the web server and it also
bean 到Web服务器，它也
registers existing servlet and filter
注册现有的servlet和过滤器
beans that it finds in the application
在应用程序中找到的bean
context with the web server so the
Web服务器的上下文
dispatcher servlet is is basically a
调度程序servlet基本上是一个
servlet implementation and like I
servlet实现和我一样
mentioned it is the central dispatcher
提到这是中央调度员
for all HTTP requests and it knows how
对于所有HTTP请求，它知道如何
to handle your HTTP requests and route
处理您的HTTP请求和路由
it to the right handler handler based on
它基于正确的处理程序
the handler mappings so when you have
处理程序映射，所以当你有
something like a request mapping a foo
类似映射foo的请求之类的东西
or a request mapping a bar on your
或将条形图映射到您的请求
controller or on one of your controller
控制器或您的一个控制器上
methods and you get a request you make a
方法，您会收到一个请求，
request via your browser
通过浏览器请求
any other client it goes through the
任何其他客户都会经历
dispatcher servlet and the dispatcher
调度程序servlet和调度程序
servlet because it's aware of all the
servlet，因为它知道所有
mappings it knows the right controller
它知道正确的控制器的映射
to route that to right so we have a
将其路由到正确的位置，所以我们有一个
running web application which is great
运行Web应用程序，这很棒
and the next thing that we should do is
接下来我们要做的是
we have everything in this one
我们在这一切
application class here so instead of
应用程序类在这里，而不是
having the stress controller within the
将压力控制器置于
application class itself we should try
应用程序类本身，我们应该尝试
and move it out of the application class
并将其移出应用程序类
because when you want to add more
因为当您想添加更多
request mappings and more functionality
请求映射和更多功能
to the controller you don't want it to
到您不想要的控制器
be all within the application class so
都在应用程序类中
I'm going to extract the controller out
我要提取控制器
into its own class here it's basically
进入自己的班级，基本上
the same for just sitting in a separate
坐在一个单独的地方也一样
class but if I run this application
类，但是如果我运行此应用程序
again you'd think it would work but I'm
再次，你会认为它会工作，但我
back to my 404 and that's because
回到我的404，那是因为
because I've moved it out string doesn't
因为我已经将其移出字符串
really know that it needs to register
真的知道它需要注册
this controller as a bean because I
该控制器作为bean，因为我
don't have the component scanning
没有组件扫描
annotation so let's go ahead and add
注释，让我们继续添加
component scanning and what the add
组件扫描以及添加的内容
component scan will do is by default it
组件扫描将默认情况下执行
will scan all the packages from the from
将从中扫描所有软件包
the package of the class that the
该类的包装
annotation is declared on so now because
之所以声明注解，是因为
application is within the example
该应用程序在示例中
package and hello controller is in that
包和hello控制器在其中
same package it should be able to find
应该可以找到的相同包装
this controller using component scanning
该控制器使用组件扫描
and we should be back to our working web
我们应该回到我们的工作网
application
应用
so yeah we're back to hello world again
是的，我们又回到了世界
this is something like when you add add
这就像当您添加添加
components and when you have the add
组件以及添加时
spring boot application annotation you
Spring Boot应用程序注释您
don't necessarily need to think about it
不一定需要考虑一下
because again it's part of that
因为这又是其中的一部分
annotation so you might not necessarily
注解，因此您不一定
have added it yourself
自己添加了
on your application but this is one one
在您的应用程序上，但这是一个
of the things that is going on behind
后面发生的事情
the scenes by default okay let's also
默认情况下，场景还可以
the next thing we should do is we've
接下来我们要做的是
also declared these beans within the
也宣布这些 Bean type 在
application class so let's try and
应用程序类，让我们尝试
extract them into their own
将它们提取到自己的
configuration classes so that it's more
配置类，以便更多
structured in a way so instead of having
如此结构化，而不是具有
all those configuration beans in the
所有这些配置 bean
application class have moved them into
应用程序类已将它们移入
this config package maybe this config
这个配置包也许这个配置
package can later be shared because this
包可以稍后共享，因为这
does seem like quite a common
确实看起来很普通
configuration for most web applications
大多数Web应用程序的配置
declaring a dispatcher servlet being
声明一个调度程序servlet
enabling web MVC and having a servlet
启用Web MVC并具有servlet
web server factory being so like I
网络服务器工厂就像我一样
mentioned before component scanning will
在组件扫描之前提到
only work from the base package of the
仅可从
of the class that the annotation is
注释所在的类
declared in and now because we've moved
宣布进入，因为我们已经搬家了
our configuration classes to a different
我们的配置类不同
package I expect that our application
包我希望我们的应用程序
will be back to an error because it's it
将回到错误，因为就是这样
can't find the servlet webserver factory
找不到Servlet Web服务器工厂
bean again so the servlet webserver
再次使用Bean，因此Servlet Web服务器
factory bean is declared in this
工厂bean在这里声明
configuration which is in a different
不同的配置
package from the one that's being
从一个正在包装
scanned so we need to explicitly tell
扫描，所以我们需要明确地告诉
string that we want to import these
我们要导入这些的字符串
configuration classes because they're
配置类，因为它们是
not being scanned by default at the
默认情况下不进行扫描
moment so let me just do that real quick
那一刻，让我快点做
so because we've moved them to a
因此，因为我们已将其移至
different package I've just added an
我刚刚添加了一个不同的软件包
explicit import statement on the
明确的导入声明
application class telling it to register
告诉它注册的应用程序类
the beans that are in this configuration
此配置中的bean
class in these configuration classes and
这些配置类中的类
that should give take us back to our
那应该带我们回到我们的
running application so if I run it it
运行应用程序，所以如果我运行它
didn't fail with the error of the
没有失败的错误
missing web server that factory bean and
缺少工厂bean和Web服务器
it's also giving us hello world
这也给我们打招呼
which is what we expect so a little bit
这是我们期望的一点
about components can the components can
关于组件可以
annotation is basically a way of telling
注释基本上是一种告诉
spring where to look for your components
Spring 在哪里寻找您的组件
so anything like your controllers or
所以像您的控制器或
your configuration classes it those will
您的配置类将那些
be automatically scanned the default is
自动扫描，默认为
the package of the class that the
该类的包装
annotation is declared on you can
注释可以声明
obviously change the default using the
显然使用
base packages or base package classes
基本包或基本包类
attributes but if you have something
属性，但如果您有东西
that looks like this so your application
看起来像这样，所以您的应用程序
is structured in this way where you have
以这种方式结构化
the demo package and then core domain
演示包，然后是核心域
and config let's say under demo and then
和配置让我们在演示下说，然后
let's say your application class is in
假设您的应用程序类在
the demo package and application has the
演示包和应用程序具有
add component scan annotation so
添加组件扫描注释，以便
everything under that demo package will
该演示包下的所有内容
be scanned by default but let's say you
默认情况下会被扫描，但假设您
were to move your config package outside
将您的配置包移到外面
of demo which is what we had in our
演示的内容
application that anything under that
那个下的东西
config package will not be scanned
配置包将不会被扫描
anymore which is what we saw and which
不再是我们所看到的
was why we had to do the manual import
这就是为什么我们必须手动导入
okay so we we have a pretty much running
好吧，我们已经运行了很多
application now and one of the things
现在申请，其中之一
that you notice here is this application
您注意到这里是此应用程序
class now has a lot of annotations which
该类现在有很多注释
doesn't give it a very clean look
看起来不干净
also these all these annotations look
这些注释也都看起来
like they could be shared by other
就像其他人可以分享
applications other web applications
应用程序其他Web应用程序
because it seems to be a pretty common
因为这似乎很普遍
pattern for web applications to do
Web应用程序要做的模式
everything that we just did so what we
我们所做的一切，所以我们
do is we'll go ahead and create a meta
我们要做的是创建一个元
annotation and the meta annotation is
注释，元注释是
nothing but an annotation which is going
只不过是注释
to be composed of these three
由这三个组成
annotations so I've called it magic
注释，所以我称之为魔术
application and as you can tell it's
应用程序，正如你所知道的
pretty similar to the add spring boot
非常类似于添加 spring boot
application its annotated with
带有注释的应用程序
the three annotations that we had
我们拥有的三个注释
previously all stuff on the application
以前应用程序上的所有内容
trust so I've just moved them behind to
信任，所以我只是将他们移至
this magic application annotation and
这个魔术应用程序注释和
things should just work as they are but
事情应该照原样工作，但
I'll run it anyway so the app is up and
无论如何，我都会运行它，以便应用程序启动并
we still see the hello world
我们仍然看到你好世界
so the next thing that I wanted to talk
所以我想谈的下一件事
about a little bit is meta annotations
大约是元注释
this is not it's not really a spring
这不是 Spring 吗
good thing but we use it quite heavily
好东西，但我们使用它相当多
within spring boot and within spring
在 spring boot 内和Spring 内
framework itself so if you are debugging
框架本身，所以如果您要调试
something that's going wrong in your
你的事情出了问题
application and you see that there's an
应用程序，您会发现有一个
annotation on in your application you
在您的应用程序中添加注释
might want to dig a bit further and look
可能想进一步挖掘并查看
at what other annotations that
还有什么其他注释
annotation pulls in so you can see
注释拉入，以便您可以看到
what's going on so I think most spring
发生了什么事，所以我认为大多数 Spring
applications can be used as meta
应用程序可以用作元
annotations you can also use them in
您也可以在其中使用注释
your own code if you want to compose
如果您想编写自己的代码
annotations into one annotation Spring
批注合并为一个批注Spring
Framework uses them quite heavily so one
框架大量使用它们，所以一个
of the examples is dress controller
例子是服装控制器
which we just used
我们刚刚使用的
there's also get mapping which you might
还有可能会映射的
be familiar with so get mapping is
熟悉所以获取映射是
actually meta annotated with add request
实际上带有添加请求的元注释
mapping but it has a method of get so
映射，但是它有一种获取方法
it's a convenient way to say I want to
这是我想表达的一种便捷方式
request mapping with a get method
使用get方法请求映射
there's also some advanced configuration
还有一些高级配置
that you get with meta annotations so if
通过元注释获得的
the the compose annotation wants to
compose注释想要
expose some of the attributes from the
暴露来自
underlying annotations it can use this
基础注释可以使用
alias for annotation on the attribute
属性上注释的别名
and then that will map to the attribute
然后将其映射到该属性
in the underlying an annotation so in
在基础注释中
this example we have the spring boot
这个例子我们有 spring boot
application annotation which is meta
应用注释是元
annotated with let's say at enable auto
假设在启用自动
configuration and that components can so
配置，组件可以这样做
the exclude attribute is an alias for
exclude属性是的别名
enable auto configurations exclude and
启用自动配置排除和
scan base packages on spring boot
在Spring Boot上扫描基本软件包
application is an alias for component
应用程序是组件的别名
and scans base packages
并扫描基本软件包
okay so I think this if you look at this
好吧，所以我认为如果你看这个
config package now it's starting to look
配置包现在开始看起来
a lot like what spring boot gives you so
很像 spring boot 给你的
you have your magic application
你有你的魔术应用程序
annotation which can map to the spring
可以映射到Spring 的注释
boot application annotation and then you
启动应用程序注释，然后您
have these configuration classes which
有这些配置类
maybe you can sort of map to the auto
也许您可以将地图映射到自动
configuration classes that you get with
您获得的配置类
spring boot but one of the things that
spring boot ，但那是一件事
you see here is that this is still
您会看到这里仍然是
hard-coded here so there's still Tomcat
在这里进行硬编码，因此仍然有Tomcat
configuration dispatcher solar
太阳能配置调度程序
configuration my an MVC configuration
配置我的MVC配置
hard-coded in the import annotation so
在导入批注中进行了硬编码，因此
what I'm gonna do before actually
我实际上要做什么
removing the hard coding let me show you
删除硬编码让我告诉你
something related to Auto configuration
与自动配置有关的内容
so instead of this import annotation
所以代替这个导入注释
here what I've done is on magic
这是我做的关于魔术的事情
application I've met annotated with this
我遇到的带有此注释的应用程序
new annotation enable magic Auto
新注释启用魔术自动
configuration and that's basically has
配置，基本上
the import for Tomcat configuration and
Tomcat配置的导入和
all the other configurations that we had
我们拥有的所有其他配置
and the reason why I did this here is
我在这里做这个的原因是
because if you want to use let's say
因为如果你想使用
component scanning but not use I mean if
组件扫描但不使用我的意思是如果
you want to use the auto configuration
您要使用自动配置
bits but not use component scanning
位，但不使用组件扫描
before the enable magic auto
在启用魔术自动之前
configuration annotations the only way
配置注释的唯一方法
to do that was to have to know about
要做那就是要知道
everything that it gets imported via
通过它导入的所有内容
this import annotation right otherwise
否则，此导入注释正确
you were stuck to using the magic
你被限制使用魔法
application annotation which would bring
应用程序注释将带来
in everything including component
在包括组件在内的所有事物中
scanning so this gives you a nice way to
扫描，这为您提供了一种不错的方法
separate component scanning from auto
将组件扫描与自动分开
configuration and which is why there's
配置，这就是为什么有
the separate annotation here so like I
像我这样的单独注释
mentioned before it's still hard coded
之前仍然提到过
here there's no way to add any sort of
这里无法添加任何形式的
logic in this import statement so I
此导入语句中的逻辑，所以我
can't do any
无能为力
thing like if Tomcat is present on the
如果Tomcat存在于
classpath then import this Tomcat
然后将classpath导入此Tomcat
configuration and things like that so
配置和类似的东西
the import annotation is actually pretty
导入批注实际上很漂亮
handy because it not only lets you
方便，因为它不仅可以让您
import configuration classes but it also
导入配置类，但也可以
gives you a way to import this thing
给你一种导入东西的方法
called import selectors so instead of
叫做导入选择器
having an import which takes all the
有一个进口，需要所有
configuration classes we can have this
配置类，我们可以有这个
import selector which basically gives
导入选择器，基本上
you an array of strings and then here
你一个字符串数组，然后在这里
you can add any kind of logical
您可以添加任何逻辑
conditionals if you want to for
有条件的，如果你想
selecting imports the reason I'm showing
选择导入我显示的原因
you this is I want to show you how what
你这是我想告诉你如何
kind of the thought process was behind
这种思想过程落后了
some of the spring boot
一些 spring boot
auto-configuration
自动配置
features that are available so this is
可用的功能，所以这是
just a road towards that and even though
只是通向那条路，即使
there is you can add logic here in in
你可以在这里添加逻辑
this import selector there's no way for
这个导入选择器没有办法
other people to contribute their own
其他人贡献自己的力量
configuration classes to this annotation
此注释的配置类
so if you've ever written your own
所以如果你曾经写过自己的
auto-configuration you you probably use
您可能使用的自动配置
the spring dot factories file in order
Spring 点工厂文件按顺序
to contribute your Auto configurations
贡献您的自动配置
to the spring good applications that use
Spring 使用的良好应用
it so let's take a look at how that
所以让我们来看看
works
作品
so the import select are now instead of
所以导入选择现在是
returning that hard-coded list of
返回的硬编码列表
configuration classes it is using the
它正在使用的配置类
spring factories loader to look for
Spring 工厂装载机寻找
configuration classes that it needs to
它需要的配置类
import that's again very similar to how
再次与导入方式非常相似
spring boot does is for all the auto
spring boot 是所有汽车的
configuration classes we list them under
配置类，我们在下面列出它们
spring load factors in spring load
Spring 载荷中的Spring 载荷系数
factories under a given key name and
给定键名的工厂和
that's how they get loaded so if we look
这就是它们的装载方式，所以如果我们看
at spring load factories which is in
在 Spring 的工厂里
meta ins you can see that the three
meta ins您可以看到这三个
configuration classes that were being
正在配置的类
imported that were being hard-coded I
导入被硬编码的我
have have now moved to this enable magic
现在已经转移到此启用魔术
auto configuration key and the import
自动配置键和导入
selector then just looks for that
选择器然后寻找
anything under that key okay so we
钥匙下的任何东西都可以，所以我们
looked a little bit about Impa looked a
有点关于Impa的样子
little bit at imports you can import
一点点进口就可以进口
regular configuration classes directly
直接常规配置类
if that's what you want to do now that's
如果那是你现在想要做的
probably most of the use cases maybe if
可能大多数用例
you're writing applications but for more
您正在编写应用程序，但更多
advanced use cases you might want to use
您可能要使用的高级用例
an import selector and for even more
导入选择器，甚至更多
advanced use cases if you want to deal
如果您想处理高级用例
directly with bean definitions you can
您可以直接使用Bean定义
also import and import bean definition
还要导入和导入bean定义
register and directly register bean
注册并直接注册bean
definitions via that and springboard
通过该定义和跳板
factus string dot factories is basically
事实上，字符串点工厂基本上是
a very simple way to discover
一种非常简单的发现方式
implementations so it's kind of like
实现，所以有点像
Javas service loader it's basically a
Java服务加载器，基本上是
very simple properties file that always
非常简单的属性文件，始终
lives under meta in spring dot factories
生活在 Spring 点工厂的meta下
so all the auto configurations will be
所以所有的自动配置
present in spring rot factories and you
现在在 Spring 腐烂工厂和你
can put it under the key of enable I
可以把它放在启用我的钥匙下
mean for Auto configuration it will be
自动配置的意思是
under enable auto configuration and it
在启用自动配置下
will be a list of everything that needs
将是所有需要的清单
to be configured
要配置
great
大
okay so one of the very important things
好，所以非常重要的事情之一
about spring boots Auto configuration is
关于 spring boot 的自动配置是
conditionals and a lot of times we hear
有条件的和很多次我们听到
things like how to spring boot know what
诸如如何启动Spring 之类的事情知道什么
to auto configure or how does spring
自动配置或如何弹跳
boot know that it needs to start up
开机知道它需要启动
Tomcat and what if Tomcat is not on the
Tomcat，如果Tomcat不在上面怎么办
class path and things like that so we
课堂路径之类的东西，所以我们
will take a look at an example of how
来看一个例子
this works here by adding this undertow
这通过添加此拖曳在这里工作
configuration so this configuration
配置，因此此配置
basically adds an undertow servlet web
基本上添加了一个Undertow Servlet Web
server factory bean we still have our
服务器工厂bean我们仍然有我们的
tomcat servlet webserver factory bean so
Tomcat的servlet的Web服务器工厂 bean 所以
now we have two web server to serve it
现在我们有两个Web服务器来服务它
works our Factory beans and if we run
工作我们的工厂 bean ，如果我们运行
this application it fails and it fails
此应用程序失败，并且失败
because not because it couldn't find a
因为不是因为找不到
servlet web server factory bean but it
servlet Web服务器工厂bean，但它
fails because it found multiple servlet
失败，因为它发现了多个servlet
web server factory beans so we need to
Web服务器工厂bean，所以我们需要
tell our application to only configure
告诉我们的应用程序仅配置
one of these based on some condition and
其中一种基于某些条件，
the way you can do that is with by using
您可以使用的方法是
the condition interface from string
字符串的条件接口
framework so we've added one condition
框架，所以我们添加了一个条件
for undertow which basically says that
基本上是说
if undertow is present on the class path
如果在课堂上出现了undertow
then add this configuration so we've
然后添加此配置，因此我们已经
written this custom configuration which
编写了这个自定义配置
checks for the presence of undertow on
检查是否存在拖曳
the class path and annotated the
类路径并注释
undertow configuration with add
带有add的underwow配置
conditional on that condition
有条件的
similarly for tomcat we've added a
同样对于tomcat，我们添加了一个
condition that checks for the presence
检查是否存在的条件
of tomcat on the class path and added a
在类路径上的tomcat并添加了一个
conditional on the tomcat configuration
以tomcat配置为条件
so now if I run the application it
所以现在如果我运行应用程序
should work because only one of these
应该工作，因为其中只有一个
will
将
and that is from cat because we have
那是从猫那里来的，因为我们有
Tomcat on our class path so this is how
Tomcat在我们的类路径上，这就是
spring boot does a lot of the auto
spring boot 做很多汽车
configuration by looking for conditional
通过寻找条件配置
on class something so let's say you have
在课堂上，所以说你有
Auto configuration for spring session
Spring 会议的自动配置
that will only kick in if spring session
只有在 Spring 会议上才会开始
is on your class path otherwise things
在你上课的路上，否则
would blow up like we just saw so even
会像我们刚刚看到的那样爆炸
though we have conditions here what we
虽然我们这里有条件
should ideally do is move these
理想情况下，应该将这些移动
conditions to a single condition because
条件到一个条件，因为
they are it is duplicated code so it's
他们是重复的代码，所以
just checking for the presence of a
只是检查是否存在
class on the class path and for that
在课程路径上的课程
let's add a custom conditional on a
让我们在上添加自定义条件
class annotation so again it's very
类注释，所以再次
similar to conditional on class in
类似于
spring but-- showing you what condition
Spring ，但是-向您展示什么情况
on rosters behind the scenes and
在幕后花名册上
conditional Antilla on a class takes
有条件的安提拉课程
this on our class condition and it's
这是在我们的课堂条件下，
basically doing what we were doing in
基本上做我们在做的事
our separate conditions for undertone
我们对底色的单独条件
and Tomcat but it's getting the class
和Tomcat，但正在上课
name attribute from the annotation and
注释中的名称属性，以及
then checking for the presence of that
然后检查那个
class on the class path so if you look
课堂上的课程，所以如果你看
at Tomcat configuration it's now it
现在是Tomcat配置
doesn't have that custom condition here
这里没有这种自定义条件
it just uses the conditional on a class
它只是在一个类上使用条件
annotation and it says that the class
注释，并说该类
name is
名字是
Tomcat so if tom carries on the class
Tomcat，所以如果tom上课
path use that otherwise for undertow
路径用于其他方式
it's the same thing
这是同一件事
so the conditional annotation is so the
所以条件注释就是
interfaces in Spring Framework and you
Spring Framework中的接口和您
can use the conditional annotation even
甚至可以使用条件注释
within your code if you want to but we
在您的代码中，如果您愿意，我们
use it pretty extensively in in spring
在 Spring 相当广泛地使用它
boots Auto configuration there are
靴子自动配置有
things like conditional on class
诸如条件上课之类的事情
conditional on being so let's say the
有条件的话，让我们说
auto configuration provides a beam
自动配置提供光束
spring boot will spring boots Auto
spring boot 将 spring boot 自动
configuration will back off if the user
如果用户退出配置
provides a beam so if your application
提供光束，因此如果您的应用程序
provides a beam spring boot will be like
提供一个梁 spring boot 会像
this thing is conditional on being so
这件事是有条件的
I'm not gonna provide my auto
我不会提供我的汽车
configuration because the user has
配置，因为用户有
already provided there's conditions also
已经提供了条件
used in Spring Framework in places like
在Spring Framework中用在
add profile so add profile is actually a
添加配置文件，因此添加配置文件实际上是
condition underneath and the conditions
下面的条件和条件
are within spring boot at least the
至少在 spring boot 内
conditions are ordered so we try to
条件是有序的，所以我们尝试
order them so that the fastest ones run
订购它们，以便最快的运行
first so I think the conditional on
首先，我认为条件是
class one has the highest precedence so
第一类的优先级最高
that will run first and if the class is
将首先运行，如果该类是
not found at all nothing under that Auto
在该汽车下根本找不到任何东西
configuration will need to be configured
配置将需要配置
and the last thing that I want the last
还有我想要的最后一件事
piece that I wanted to show in a spring
我想在 Spring 展示的作品
boot application is adding a property so
引导应用程序添加了一个属性，因此
in in spring boot you have this thing
在 spring boot 里你有这个东西
called configuration properties where
称为配置属性，其中
you can specify a property in an
您可以在
external configuration and that that
外部配置以及那个
gets bound to your configuration
绑定到您的配置
properties class so to build towards
属性类，以便向
that let's say we have this Tomcat
假设我们有这个Tomcat
configuration so for starters before
配置，以便初学者之前
adding any of the thing that the
添加任何东西
configuration properties does what I've
配置属性可以完成我的工作
done is just use the value annotation
完成只是使用值注释
from Spring Framework and it will look
来自Spring Framework，它将看起来
for a property called port so if you
对于称为端口的属性，如果
want to configure your port or something
想要配置您的端口或其他东西
other than 8080 you can use that and
除了8080以外，您还可以使用
that'll work so if I run the application
这样就可以了，如果我运行该应用程序
in actually I haven't specified the
实际上我没有指定
application properties yet so let me
应用程序属性，所以让我
check out the next commit but before
在下一次提交之前签出
that if I run this application it fails
如果我运行此应用程序，它将失败
with a number format exception and I
有数字格式异常，我
think that's because I don't have the
认为那是因为我没有
property sources placeholder
财产来源占位符
configuration so
这样配置
I have added this configuration for the
我已经为
property sources placeholder configure
属性来源占位符配置
again this is something you don't need
再次，这是你不需要的东西
to typically do this is all happening
通常会发生这种情况
behind the scenes but just to give you
幕后，只是为了给你
an idea of what's going on behind the
关于背后发生的事情的想法
scenes this should now work so the
场景现在应该可以工作了，所以
application is up and it's still running
应用程序启动并且仍在运行
on port 8080 which was the default which
在端口8080上，这是默认设置
is again the default that we've used in
再次是我们使用的默认值
in the value annotation if port is not
如果端口不是，则在值注释中
found so if we were to change that so
发现，如果我们要改变这一点
I've added this file called magic tor
我已经添加了这个名为magic tor的文件
properties and specify the port 9090 so
属性并指定端口9090，因此
if if I run that I maybe some of you
如果我跑了，我也许你们中的一些人
expect that it will run on 1990 now
预计它将在1990年开始运行
because I've added it as a property but
因为我已经将其添加为属性，但是
it's actually still starting up on port
它实际上仍在港口启动
8080 so there's more configuration to
8080所以有更多配置
process a property so we've added a file
处理属性，所以我们添加了一个文件
but nothing is really processing it at
但实际上并没有真正处理它
the moment in a spring boot application
Spring Boot应用程序中的那一刻
if you add an application or properties
如果添加应用程序或属性
file or an application or EML file that
文件或应用程序或EML文件
automatically gets processed for you
自动为您处理
behind the scenes but here we need to
在幕后，但在这里我们需要
add that configuration ourselves so
自己添加该配置，以便
there's this environment post processor
有这个环境后处理器
that that is a way that is available
那是一种可用的方式
with any spring boot application and you
与任何 spring boot 应用程序，你
can implement that to add things to the
可以实现将东西添加到
environment if you want to in this case
环境，如果您想在这种情况下
we're just going to read the magic dot
我们只是要读魔术点
properties file from the classpath and
来自类路径的属性文件和
get the properties from that file and
从该文件获取属性，然后
store it as a property source in the
将其存储为属性源
environment
环境
so now finally after all this
所以现在终于这一切了
configuration the server has started on
服务器已启动的配置
port 90 90 which is what we specified in
端口90 90这是我们在中指定的
our properties file but again the value
我们的属性文件，但再次值
annotation is not typesafe and
注释不是类型安全的，
configuration properties is a good
配置属性很好
alternative towards that to the value
价值的替代选择
annotation so even though we do have our
注释，所以即使我们有我们的
server up on port 90 90 here we should
服务器在端口90 90上，我们应该
go ahead and add something that makes
继续并添加一些使
use of the type safety features so
使用类型安全功能，以便
instead of using the add value
而不是使用增加值
annotation now we are using this class
现在我们正在使用此类
server properties so in server
服务器中的服务器属性
properties we have a port which you can
属性，我们有一个端口，您可以
then set to whatever value you want
然后设置为您想要的任何值
so in spring dots in magical properties
所以在 Spring 的神奇特性
we still have 4 90 90 and we've used
我们还有4 90 90，我们已经使用了
server properties in the Tomcat
Tomcat中的服务器属性
configuration class but again if I run
配置类，但是如果我再次运行
this it fails because it says that the
这失败了，因为它说
Tomcat configuration needs a being of
Tomcat配置需要
type config dot server properties but it
键入配置点服务器属性，但是
doesn't find that bean and that's
找不到那个 bean ，那是
because nothing is really creating that
因为没有什么能真正创造出
bean for you in this application so we
bean在这个应用程序中为您服务，所以我们
need to do that ourselves
需要自己做
and the way I've done it here which is
我在这里做的方式是
kind of similar to the way spring to
有点类似于 Spring
spring boot does it is using sorry I
spring boot 是使用对不起我
just need to look for the class this
只需要找这个班
enable magic properties register so we
启用魔术属性注册，所以我们
looked a little bit of at the import
看起来有点进口
beam definition registers that you can
您可以使用光束定义寄存器
use in your import annotations and this
在您的导入注释中使用
Ana this enable magic properties
安娜这启用魔术属性
register is an import bean register and
register是导入bean注册，并且
what it does is it basically registers
它所做的基本上是注册
any beam that is annotated with hold on
按住不放注释的任何光束
sorry
抱歉
so in our enable magic properties
所以在我们启用魔术属性
annotation we've specified that we want
我们指定了我们想要的注释
to enable the server properties class so
启用服务器属性类
what that means is that the enable magic
这意味着启用魔法
properties import beam definition
属性导入梁定义
registrar will register this beam and it
注册服务商将对此光束进行注册
will also bind the properties from the
还将绑定来自
properties file to this class so it's
属性文件到此类，因此
basically got an import statement on and
基本上在
says that it's importing the enable
说它正在导入启用
magic properties registrar and the
魔术属性注册商和
registrar's registrar has all the logic
注册商的所有逻辑
for the binding that goes on when that
对于那时候进行的绑定
beam is created so I've used this binder
梁已创建，因此我使用了该活页夹
from spring boot too and when you have
从 spring boot ，当你有
configuration properties in your spring
Spring 的配置属性
boot application there is an enable or
引导应用程序有一个启用或
enable configuration properties
启用配置属性
annotation which you might have used to
您可能曾经使用过的注释
enable your own properties my own
启用自己的属性
properties and behind the scenes this is
属性和幕后这是
what's happening there is an import beam
发生了什么事，有进口光束
definition registrar which will register
定义注册商将注册
the beam and bind the properties from
束并绑定属性
that it finds from application door
它从应用程序门中找到
properties to that beam so
该光束的特性
if we run it now we should have the
如果我们现在运行它，我们应该拥有
server properties being created and it
正在创建的服务器属性及其
should have been bound with port 9090
应该已经绑定了9090端口
which will which is what is specified in
这将在中指定
the properties file so just a quick look
属性文件，以便快速浏览
at this configure config package here a
在这个配置配置包这里
lot of these things like the conditional
这些事情很多，例如有条件的
on a class the enable magic auto
在课堂上启用自动魔术
configuration enable magic properties
配置启用魔术属性
magic application and things that we
魔术应用程序和我们要做的事情
just added they look very similar to the
刚刚添加，它们看起来与
annotations that springboard gives you
跳板为您提供的注释
so we just basically created an
所以我们基本上创建了一个
application from scratch and added stuff
从头开始添加应用程序
one by one that you would have got out
一件一件地走出去
of the box with spring boot but
装有 spring boot 的包装盒，但
hopefully this gave you an idea of what
希望这给你一个想法
hap what needs to be configured behind
hap需要在后面配置什么
the scenes so that you get this running
场景，以便您运行
application and a faster getting started
应用程序和更快的入门
experience
经验
so again just to recap the conditionals
所以再次回顾一下条件
they map to conditional on class the
他们以班级为条件
magic application was the meta
魔术应用是元
annotation so spring good application is
注释，因此 Spring 良好的应用是
also a meta annotation if you find that
如果发现
you're having issues with component
您的组件有问题
scanning you can always look at the dig
扫描您可以随时查看挖掘
deeper into the component scan aspect or
更深入地了解组件扫描方面
you can dig deeper into the enable
您可以更深入地研究
auto-configuration aspect of the spring
Spring 的自动配置方面
boot application annotation enable magic
引导应用程序注释启用魔术
Auto configuration is the annotation
自动配置是注释
that was importing our configuration
那是导入我们的配置
classes in this application in spring
Spring 该应用程序中的类
boot it Maps to enable auto
启动它映射以启用自动
configuration which brings in all the
配置带来了所有
auto configuration that is registered
已注册的自动配置
there are register in spring load
Spring 负载中有寄存器
factories and the start dot star
工厂和起点星
configuration classes like Tomcat
像Tomcat这样的配置类
configuration undertook an undertow
配置承担了责任
configuration that we added basically
我们基本添加的配置
maps to the auto configurations like the
映射到自动配置，例如
auto configuration for servlet so
servlet的自动配置
servlet Auto configuration which will
servlet自动配置
add the Tomcat beans and the undertow
添加Tomcat bean和undertow
beans for you so basically the idea was
bean 给你，所以基本上这个想法是
to show you that there is no such thing
告诉你没有这样的事情
as magic
作为魔术
just built everything from scratch and
从头开始构建所有内容，
we were able to build everything with
我们能够用
code so there's no magic it's that
代码，所以没有魔法
everything is in code and for debugging
一切都在代码中并用于调试
spring applications or spring buta
Spring 应用或Spring buta
applications just follow the breadcrumbs
应用程序只是跟随面包屑
look at what annotations are on the
看一下什么是注释
application look at what imports are
应用程序看看什么是进口
being used or what import selectors are
正在使用或什么是导入选择器
being used and then you can put
被使用，然后你可以把
breakpoints in that and debug it if you
断点并调试它，如果您
need to Springs out factories is a way
需要涌出工厂是一种方法
to for you to contribute more Auto
为您贡献更多的汽车
configuration if you're writing that and
配置，如果您正在编写和
conditions is the way spring boot Auto
条件是Spring 启动方式
configuration knows when to back off
配置知道何时退出
when to contribute certain beans and
何时贡献某些 Bean type 和
things like that also it's all open
这样的事情也都开放
source so use the source if you need to
源，因此如果需要，请使用源
for debugging and hopefully that will
进行调试，希望它将
help you develop better applications
帮助您开发更好的应用程序
thank you
谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]